stkate.edu 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy | St. Kate's

## St. Catherine University's data collection privacy practices.

#### This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following: 

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. The choices that are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

* * *

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

St. Catherine University is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone or any organization. 

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization. As many colleges and universities do, on a limited basis we partner with organizations that help us contact and communicate with prospective students. In these limited cases, the organizations operate on our behalf. We share your information with these organizations but never sell or rent your information.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email or phone for purposes of furthering your access and pursuit of the educational opportunities available through St. Catherine University.

### Your Access to and Control of Information 

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided at the end of this policy: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the St. Catherine University website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

Wherever we collect your information (e.g. e-mail, phone, US postal service address), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page you are accessing.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform specific job tasks (for example, processing or making decisions about an application for admission) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. 

### Cookies 

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. A cookie is a small text file that is sent to your computer when you first visit. The cookie is stored on your computer and allows you to be recognized when you visit again later. 

St. Catherine University occasionally uses remarketing services (such as Google, Facebook and LinkedIn) to advertise on third-party websites to previous visitors of our site. Third-party vendors place cookies on users' browsers for targeted advertising purposes and serve ads to locations such as the Google search results page or any site in the Google Display Network based on someone's past website visits.

Data such as identification of your internet browser or computer operating system may be collected for targeted advertising. This information is collected to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data to facilitate content improvements. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings and opt out of the additional use of cookies by visiting this site.

Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. The generic information we collect is based on IP address, which is the location of a computer or network, and is not linked to your specific email address or other personally identifiable information in any of the reports or other material compiled by St. Catherine University. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, doing so may prevent you from using the full functionality of our websites. 

Some St. Catherine University websites may contain links to external websites not owned by, or officially affiliated with, St. Catherine University in any way. St. Catherine University is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Updates 

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Updates will be posted on this page. 

* * *

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at **651-690-6829** or via email at [**webmaster@stkate.edu**](mailto:webmaster@stkate.edu).
